PACHINKO
They're asking for a fight,
the way these pins are tuned.
Eight spins per 1K is frigging brutal.
And a 1,500-spin dry spell,
on a fresh machine?!
Where's my damn jackpot?!
This thing deserves a good smack.
Pisses me off.
Big chance!
92%! 92%! 92%!
Pull
Pull!
This has gotta be it...
Okay, it's in the bag!
Is that all the strength you can muster?
No way.
Please save it.
It's not over yet.
It's a bust!
Beef Bowl Free Size Upgrade
Chance Akaishi here with
another day of lucky spins!
Man, ya don't see this often, huh?
A parlor so empty, they don't
even use numbered tickets!
Let's dig up some chances!
Ah, m'bad.
Ah, my bad.
Beef Bowl Free Size Upgrade
Why don't we trade?
1,000 yen.
Also, big guy...
Do you make big money?
Doing this NewTube stuff.
Well, I guess...
Very nice.
Good morning from the dead of night!
A New Member Joins! DEAD or ALIVE
Mayonaka Punch! Live here!
Ichiko!
I'm Fu.
For today's video...
Real Wasabi
If we eat nagashi somen
as a three-in-one act...
...will we become better friends?!
All right!
I'm gonna go fast here!
Bring it on!
Hey, Ichiko! To your right!
Yes!
Fu, that's my head!
S-Sorry!
Over here?
That's my chin! No, my boobs!
Up, up, up!
Live-sama, here's some grated ginger!
Wait, that's spicy!
Fu, let's crank up the speed.
S-Sure!
That's the stuff!
Live-sama, here's some grated wasabi!
Real Wasabi
Are you all right?!
There, you're done.
Just when it got to the good part!
You need to keep it down.
Masaki's trying to think of ideas for videos.
Did you say something?
No, Ichiko was just rewatching the
vid we uploaded the other day.
It's super funny, Masaki!
Well, I did come up with the idea,
shoot the video, and edit it.
Of course it's funny.
Then how come no one's
watching such a funny video?
Crap!
Ichiko! I'm hungry!
Isn't it about time we had dinner?
Right away, Live-sama!
Are you angry?
I'm not angry.
You're totally angry.
I'm panicking!
It's been three weeks
since we started the channel!
And look at this!
Um... Look at what?
We've put out so many videos!
And forget a million subscribers—
we don't even have 10,000 views in total!
C'mon, we only just started.
Still!
Anyway, we can't do anything
if I don't come up with ideas.
So let me think!
Mayonaka Punch
217 subscribers
Super Low-Cost??
Cinderella
Outer Loop? Inner Loop?!
A Disputed Verdict?!
Pitch Dark
rella | Cosplaying on a Shoestring Budget
(Actually Just Covered in Ashes)
Shenanigans Galore! Yamanote Line Game
with 3 Players!
We're Night Owls... And We Spent
48 Hours with the Lights Off!!
Content Ideas
Have a clear topic
Easy to understand (can tell from thumbnail)
Relatable
Take it seriously
Why can't I come up with ideas for content?
It used to be easier...
Wait, these are the girls from Chu-Chu Girls who blew up before.
Why'd you start a new channel??
I liked it better when you were
the Chu-Chu Girls
Everyone's still cute, but you used
to play to Live's strengths better
Something smells good.
Liver and chives! Liver and chives!
Okay, everyone, please take your seats!
Awesome! Time for food!
Masaki, why don't you take a break?
Growl...
All right, then, all together now!
Thanks for the food!
Thanks.
Man, this is good!
She can really pack it in.
I bet a video of her eating would do well.
Hold on, so do vampires need to eat food, too?
Huh?
Nah, not at all.
Then why do you eat every day?
Eating meals together is important!
Sure, why not?
Hey, Masaki!
Have you thought up anything yet? Well?
Not yet. Why?
I came up with an idea that's sure to be a hit.
Wanna know what it is?
Sure.
Here it is!
Ichiko tries on a strawberry costume!
Nope.
What?
How about a banana?
Ichiko tries on a banana—
Double nope.
Then what about—
Nope to everything.
Why not?!
Listen here.
Do you know how much those costumes cost?
I'm trying to take all that into account here!
Something low-budget that sounds a little
familiar, but with its own original twist!
That's how you come up with content!
It's not about suggesting
things all willy-nilly!
Take your banana and shove it!
I'll shove liver and chives down my throat!
There, there.
How naïve of you.
Originality comes after you squeeze,
and squeeze,
and keep on squeezing...
until you're left with that one last drop!
Who're you?!
The name's Tokage.
A wayward vampire out on the hunt for money!
There are more vampires?!
Tokage.
Eating for free without paying your share...
I won't stand for it!
Here.
Life ain't as simple as you think.
It's a little like gambling.
The bigger the thrill,
the deeper in you find yourself.
As you grow more numb, you seek more thrills.
And this coupon gives you a free upgrade,
but the beef bowl itself doesn't come free.
Nothing but an empty promise.
What's your point, already?
Just admit that you're broke.
Heck, you just want easy money
without working for it.
Is that all you have to say
after twenty years, Live?
Don't patronize me just because
you're a couple of centuries older.
That's a big difference.
Hey, you're Masaki, right?
What?
I saw your little channel.
With its lame, stale, cookie-cutter videos.
What a joke!
Wh-What?!
I want a 50/50 split of the profits.
Let's work together!
What?!
Idea Proposals
1. Pachinko Crossing: New Horizons
~The Dead Tree Comes to Life
with Pachinko Machines!!~
2. Proverbs on Life
~Tokage-sama's Gambling Wisdom~
3. Everybody Eat Up
~Don't Hesitate, Eat!
Eat, and You'll See!!!~
If you're going to use vampires
hiding their powers for NewTube,
you'll need outrageous content like this...
Hey, what's the big idea?!
Outrageous, my ass!
All you did was give them weird names!
Don't judge a book by its title!
Would you discriminate against
rice balls based on looks?!
What?
It's what's inside that's important!
Filling
The filling is what matters!
You're just a brat in your twenties!
I've lived two hundred years longer than you,
so don't act like you know better!
Two hundred years older,
and this is the best you can do?
Go on, tell us, then!
What amazing ideas do you have?!
Y-You asked for it!
I said that, but I can't think up squat.
Masaki, panicking will do you no good—
I know that!
I'm done for.
The well's run dry.
All right!
Leave it to me!
Let's go find some content!
Content!
Conte...
This door...
W-Wrong place!
Let's move on, 'kay?
Why?
Don't even worry about it!
Could this be content?
H-H-Hey, what are you doing?!
Content! It's gotta be!
It's stuck.
What stinks?!
What's the big idea?!
That's my line!
Let us have a peek inside.
Nuh-uh!
You're invading my privacy!
What, do you have something to hide?!
O-O-Of course not!
Help me, Live!
No!
I've tried so hard to pretend
this room doesn't exist!
You can't be serious!
And I'd like to keep it that way!
Live.
You want to suck me dry, don't you?
Pretty please!
What in the world?
Th-This...
Don't look!
I'm dying of shame!
This is it!
How long's this room been like this?
Since this house was built, pretty much.
This might be just what we need!
Live! Help me out here!
Okay.
Combustible Waste
The title of our next video is...
"Centuries of Household Trash?!"
A Lady's
Way Filthy Room
"What's the Pawn Value
of a Lady's Filthy Room?!"
How Much is Centuries
of Trash Really Worth?
Sensei!
Is there really a demand for that?
Live!
Cleaning videos have their die-hard fans!
Throwing out piled-up trash is
already plenty entertaining,
but Tokage's built up
so much over the years,
we might end up stumbling
across some real treasure!
In other words, we can do big numbers,
roll in the dough, and get this room clean.
It's a win-win-win situation!
Now that's what I call content!
W-Wait a minute.
You're saying my garbage is worth money?
That's right.
Maybe.
Definitely!
Hell yeah!
Let's get this show on the road!
Hey, everyone, you need to
separate all of this trash!
Huh? What now, Ichiko?
We're sorting everything just fine!
Listen up!
You need to carefully separate trash
for a greener Earth!
But there are plastic bottles in your bag
of combustible waste, Ichiko-chan.
What are you going on about?
Plastic bottles count as organic waste!
I saw it on TV, you know!
When you burn plastic bottles,
the polypolyvinyl turns the flame green,
which makes it a green initiative!
Waste Separation Chart
Combustible
Non-Combustible
Recyclable
Hazardous
Organic waste
Wastepaper
Wood chips
etc.
Ceramics
Metal items
Bottles
Cans
Plastic
bottles
containers
Used paper
Cardboard
Old clothes
Batteries
Fluorescent
lamps
Small
appliances
Plastic bottles are recyclable waste.
Whoopsie!
I forgot I can't read kanji—
Hey, how old is this?
I forget.
I think about eighty years?
Wow!
It might be worth a lot.
Seriously? This thing?
M-My money...
Tokage, what about this?
Oh!
That teacup used to belong
to Sen-what's-his-face—
Ack! A bug!
I think this... and this are junk.
So much for treasure.
Wait, we've been at it for five hours,
and it's still this bad?
Damn it.
It really is just worthless trash!
If we can't pawn this off,
how about a super-endurance—
Hey, hey!
Be careful what you throw out!
But it's all rotted away or broken!
You don't know that yet!
If it's worth anything, we need to
make sure we get our money!
Oh, sorry.
Forget all that for now.
I'm changing it to a
super-endurance cleaning video.
What?
You...
You... You...
You've gotta be kidding me!
Tokage! We're filming!
Money! Money!
I want some damn money!
Oh, no!
Ichiko! Fu!
Open the windows!
Cool it already!
Money!
Wow.
You asked for it!
Tokage doesn't stand a chance
against Live-sama!
All right!
Ugh!
I see you're shooting a video.
Of our powers.
Um...
Shigeyuki-san, you see—
It's Yuki!
Don't you dare call me Shigeyuki, human!
Masaki!
Yuki-sama doesn't like being called Shigeyuki!
Her real name may be Shigeyuki, but...
You, there!
Shut your trap!
Whoa, whoa. Let's calm down.
I warned you, didn't I?
That you'd be erased
if you made videos of our powers.
I may have used my powers,
but that was unavoidable!
I won't take any excuses!
Hand over the video data.
I-I refuse.
Hand it over.
Or would you rather
I destroyed the entire camera?
Masaki...
Hey, what's this?
The hell's going on?
See for yourself.
My money!
Fu.
There's another camera in that
filthy room, isn't there?
Bring it here.
Yes!
Hey, let go of it!
No way!
If I hand this over, everyone's hard
work will have been for nothing!
Masaki...
Money...
You really don't know when to quit.
Oh, yes. I never did get a chance
to thank you for last time.
I can still smell it to this day!
I'll stop asking for free item coupons!
I'm fine with just the upgrade coupons!
Stop it! I promise we won't use our powers
when filming again, so please don't!
Get off of me!
I'm begging you, Yuki.
Pretty please!
Are you being serious?
Fine.
No means no!
You won't escape your punishment!
Guilty!
Yuki, what's this?
If you finish all of it, I won't tell
Mother about what happened today.
But if you happen to leave any...
What if we eat every last one, then?
I just said I won't tell Mother—
That's not enough.
What?
Not enough at all.
You do realize we ended up
having to scrap all of our footage?
Footage that would have made us money!
And what's your point?
If we eat all of this,
I want a fat stack of cash!
Absolutely not!
Say, Yuki...
We don't use our vampire powers
when we eat, do we?
I suppose not.
Which means it's okay
to take a video of it, right?
Huh? I guess...
I'm filming this?
Everybody eat up.
Don't hesitate, eat. Eat, and you'll see.
3. Everybody Eat Up
~Don't Hesitate, Eat!
Eat, and You'll See!!!~
Masaki!
We've gotta do it!
Leave it to me when it comes
to food... To mukbang!
Hold that thought!
There's nothing compelling about a
video of you eating a pile of raw garlic!
Whatever! Just film it!
If it flops, I'll beg on my knees,
or stomach, or whatever you want!
I don't care! Get to eating, already!
Live-sama!
Mukbang is fun, mukbang is fun...
Okay!
Here we go, everyone!
Roll camera!
Good morning from the dead of night!
Mayonaka Punch! Live here...
F-For today's video...
Today's segment is, "Everybody Eat Up!
Don't Hesitate, Eat! Eat, and You'll See!"
All right, everyone! Time to confront
the food we all hate: garlic!
Off we go!
We're in this together, Live-sama!
H-Hey!
Act like it's a little tasty!
That's simply not possible.
They're vampires.
Then force a smile, at least!
How're you holding up, Live-shi?
Don't hesitate to dig into that garlic.
How about you, Ichiko-shi?
Doing good, Fu-shi?
Cuckoo! Cuckoo!
Bing-bong!
Good morning from Fu-chan—
Cuckoo! Cuckoo!
Y'know, I used to think hand lotion
was the same thing as toothpaste.
Then I realized that was the fate of the
old lady in the Grimms' fairy tale,
to be born from a duck egg—
Ichiko, you're out.
What a shocker.
Slash-and-burn?
I prefer chateaubriand, thanks.
Make the peanut gallery pipe down!
Garlic is yummy. Garlic is yummy.
Garlic is yummy.
Oh, look!
I spy a cutie-pie with tasty-looking blood!
That's enough.
I'm stopping the camera.
You can't be serious!
If I quit here, I can't call myself a gambler!
We're not gambling jack here!
And this video stinks!
It's just a miserable sight!
Dead or alive.
An extreme gamble with my life on the line!
Just watch me!
Tokage...
Whammo!
I have not one scrap of garlic
left on my entire plate!
I swear, what a silly girl you are.
None of this makes any sense.
Total nonsense.
Tokage Cleans
Her Plate
It's very dangerous for normal people
to eat large amounts of raw garlic.
Don't try this at home <3
It's very dangerous for normal people
to eat large amounts of raw garlic.
Don't try this at home <3
There, you're done.
She didn't even turn into pure-white ash yet!
You've been rewatching it for three days!
It's still funny every single time!
Well, I did come up with the idea,
had the video shot, and had it edited.
Of course it's funny.
My own genius scares me sometimes.
But it's purely by coincidence
that that video...
Just look at the numbers.
Cold, hard hits.
Mayonaka Punch
12k views
1 week ago
Subscribe
Endless Garlic Hell
Doing the Impossible
Everybody Eat Up ~Don't Hesitate, Eat! Eat, and You'll See!!!~
Wow, 12,000 views.
Easy peasy, lemon squeezy for me!
Oh, they're here.
Heya!
Second floor, room in the back.
Um, what's all this, exactly?
Huh? Didn't I mention it?
Starting today, Masaki's moving in with us.
I can't wait!
What?!
But why now?
Now that we have momentum,
I can't let this chance slip away!
I'll live with you, shoot tons of videos,
and ride this wave to turn our channel
into a powerhouse in no time!
That's the plan!
There you have it.
M-Makes sense.
Okay, you're helping, too!
Y-Yes!
Sure!
That's one hell of a dream you got there.
Let me join your little group.
I assumed you already had.
With that settled, let's talk
profit share for our last video!
A 50/50 share, like we agreed on!
Don't play dumb!
Where's my slice of the pie?
Um, that won't come into play for a while.
What?!
Chance Akaishi told me...
MayoPan isn't even monetized yet!
That's not what you promised!
I didn't promise you squat!
I'm leaving all of you!
Hand over my money!
Tokage
Sent you a sticker
Goodnight
Pay me, pay me, pay me!
Masaki here!
MayoPan's got a new member!
Who's that?
You, duh.
That's right! It's me, Tokage!
Honestly, I don't know if this will work out!
Seriously? Try harder!
Next time: "The Star of the Next Video is Who?"
The Star of the Next Video is Who?
The Star
What? It's me?